export const engQuestions = [
  {
    prompt: 'The main argument in the report is ___ correct.',
    answerA: 'supposedly',
    answerB: 'primarily',
    answerC: 'up to a point',
    answerD: 'fundamentaly',
    correctAnswer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'There are about thirty ___ so people sitting in the bus.',
    answerA: 'so',
    answerB: 'but',
    answerC: 'or',
    answerD: 'and',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'By the time we ___ at the parking lot, it was already full.',
    answerA: 'turned up',
    answerB: 'got through',
    answerC: 'applied to',
    answerD: 'filled in',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which one of the following words is spelt correctly?',
    answerA: 'mischievous',
    answerB: 'mischevios',
    answerC: 'mischevious',
    answerD: 'mischievous',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which is the correct spelling of this synonym of the word RANKING?',
    answerA: 'hirarchy',
    answerB: 'hiearchy',
    answerC: 'hierarchy',
    answerD: 'hiararchy',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which one is spelled correctly?',
    answerA: 'questionnaire',
    answerB: 'questionaire',
    answerC: 'questionnare',
    answerD: 'questionare',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which one is the synonym of the word PALTRY',
    answerA: 'anniversary',
    answerB: 'proposal',
    answerC: 'insignificant',
    answerD: 'forecast',
    correctAnswer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: '___ he wouldnâ€™t wait at the lobby for ages, I told my assistant to let him.',
    answerA: 'Hence',
    answerB: 'Because',
    answerC: 'In case',
    answerD: 'In order that',
    correctAnswer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Some have difficulty ___ numbers ___ two until the age of three or four.',
    answerA: 'grasping / greater than',
    answerB: 'to grasp / to',
    answerC: 'in grasping / fewer',
    answerD: 'of grasping / of',
    correctAnswer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Your father should not put so much pressure on you. He must not choose your friends, ___',
    answerA: 'as well',
    answerB: 'though',
    answerC: 'too',
    answerD: 'either',
    correctAnswer: 'D'
  },
]
